bluechillies.com 2019-04-25

# Privacy Policy : Your Freeware and Shareware Download Destination! : BlueChillies.com

**BlueChillies.com** is committed to protecting your privacy online. We are also committed to providing you with the very best experience we can on our Web site. In order to enhance your experience at our site we gather certain personal information about you that helps us customize our content to your tastes and preferences. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our Web site. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. 

**BlueChillies.com** collects and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site, and to help identify you. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information, and for other purposes. 

**BlueChillies.com** collects some personal information when you initially access our site. We may ask for your name, e-mail address, zip code, and country. The more information you share with us (and the more accurate it is), the better we are able to enhance and customize your experience on our site. The data required to activate your membership is used solely for the account you maintain with us. All real data you provide to us is kept strictly confidential. We does not sell, rent, or trade your personal information with others.

**BlueChillies.com** run some survey and submission form in which we ask the visitors for their email address. This email address we obtain from visitors will not be sold or shared with any third party. All information gathered is used for internal purposes only. 

**BlueChillies.com** use some outside ad companies to display ads on the site. These ads contain cookies or web beacons. Cookies received with text or banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies in your browser settings.

**BlueChillies.com** has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our servers have strict security in place to prevent an intruder from retrieving personal information about our users. Staff overlook server access daily to ensure the above holds true. 

**BlueChillies.com** site contains links to other sites and file downloads from other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by **BlueChillies.com** as outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site you can contact us.
